

MOHAN

Crew, Graphics Designer Motion Graphics & 3D modeling Arts





EDUCATION

Graduation **B.A Programme IGNOU** 2017 - 2020

Graphic Design

Maya Academy of **Advanced Creativity**

Graphics Designer Motion Graphics & 3D modeling Arts 2022 - 2024

EXPERTISE

- Guest Handling
- trainer
- Team leading
- · Critical Thinking
- · Communication Skills
- Digital Marketing
- Negotiation
- · graphic desiger
- Video Editor
- 3D Artist

LANGUAGE

- English
- · Hindi

PROFILE

I Am 5Years Working In The McDonalds India As A Crew. I Have really very good and very amazing experience. And Highly skilled guest handling and working with a team leading. I Am Professional Video Editor, creating unique designs and video with expert editing, color grading, motion graphics, graphic designing and visual effects. i have a huge passion for creating impactful more experierce for guset handling and graphic designs and visual storytelling.

WORK EXPERIENCE

McDonalds india

2018 - 2023

Crew

- · Working with the wider development team.
- Train a new crew members. How to do a work every station with processor

DREAMCRAFT ANIMATIONS

2023 - 2024

Graphic Desiger, Motion Graphic & 3D Artist

- Working with the wider development team.
- · Video Editor, creating unique designs and video with expert editing, color grading, motion graphics, graphic designing and visual effects.

REFERENCES